Template.qanda.helpers({
  candidateQuestions: function () {
    return [
      { 'questionStub' : 'Quality of Life',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Incidunt atque assumenda, facilis a corporis enim ex praesentium, accusamus. Ipsa, aspernatur laudantium eos voluptas. Dolorem aperiam minima necessitatibus quod, itaque dolor.', 'question' : '1. What three things would you advocate for that would increase the quality of life for Hamiltonians, and attract new residents to the city?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Economy',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Quasi beatae sequi cupiditate facilis deserunt, voluptatem modi delectus necessitatibus earum voluptatibus molestias nostrum assumenda, illum, ab amet molestiae minus, maxime. Et.', 'question' : '2. Hamilton has a tax base imbalance (77% residential vs. 23% commercial/industrial in 2013), coupled with an industrial vacancy rate of less than 2%. How will you overcome these challenges to grow the city’s economy and attract additional corporate investment?' }, 
      { 'questionStub' : 'Industry Clusters',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Officiis, similique illum, temporibus veritatis quis repudiandae obcaecati, maiores nihil optio, labore quae tempore numquam possimus recusandae quaerat ipsam unde tempora aliquam.', 'question' : '3. The City of Hamilton’s Economic Development division has identified several industry clusters with high potential (advanced manufacturing; agribusiness & food processing, clean tech; creative industries; and life sciences). What is the mayor’s role in attracting investment in these clusters?' },
      { 'questionStub' : 'Education & Youth',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Ratione facere veritatis est deleniti nulla sit eligendi modi inventore totam sunt, ab, saepe voluptas velit nam quod beatae, earum corrupti recusandae.', 'question' : '4. Hamilton has some of the top post-secondary education institutions in Canada. What role would you play in the attraction, engagement and retention of youth in the city of Hamilton?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Red Tape',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Hic deleniti fugiat ea voluptates obcaecati consequuntur tempore blanditiis maxime sint temporibus dicta aliquid laboriosam tenetur quibusdam molestiae eaque, amet iure, nisi.', 'question' : '5. Our members business ventures rely heavily on the ease with which their project applications are reviewed and processed by City staff; as well as the clarity and quality of information available to current and prospective business owners. Considering “government red tape” is a perennial election topic, what ideas and priorities do you have to foster more effective interaction between businesses and City Hall?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Business Community',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Sunt sint non accusamus molestias aut est obcaecati esse soluta, quasi repellendus eaque velit optio illum neque incidunt aliquid voluptatibus omnis. Quod!', 'question' : '6. As Mayor, what steps will you take to improve and facilitate the voice of the business community with all levels of government?'}, 
      { 'questionStub' : 'Transportation',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Ea repellendus molestias, porro velit quis esse quas at voluptate, unde beatae, totam fugiat quibusdam molestiae blanditiis eos! Saepe voluptate quia assumenda.', 'question' : '7. As mayor what is your strategic vision for the future of Hamilton’s Transportation Infrastructure? This includes but is not limited to: The future of the Light Rail Transit initiative, Complete Streets conversion, Commercial freight infrastructure etc. '},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Industrial Development',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Ad voluptate, eum laudantium placeat similique accusamus obcaecati voluptates soluta deleniti earum optio, esse voluptatibus ipsam ex nesciunt facilis doloribus eos, dolores.', 'question' : '8. Hamilton has significant potential for industrial and commercial growth close to its transportation hubs, namely the Hamilton International Airport and the Hamilton Port Authority. What kind of development would you like to see around these hubs, especially the current and future brownfield vacancies at Hamilton’s Waterfront Industrial areas?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Housing Affordability',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Debitis sed, aliquam corporis maiores iusto rerum, at error incidunt commodi id facilis impedit, porro dolor repellendus consequuntur ratione tempora. Reprehenderit, quam.', 'question' : '9. The Hamilton commercial and residential real estate market is facing pressures such as limited land availability in the urban boundary and increasing land values, and affordability will become a greater challenge over the next few years. Furthermore, the expansion in scope and pricing of development application fees and development charges has put additional pressure on the real estate affordability. Lastly, 2015 will see a review of, among a number of other related plans, the Greenbelt, with an eye to modifying or expanding its limits.  What are your thoughts on ensuring that businesses and home buyers will continue to find affordability and choice in Hamilton?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Housing Opportunities',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Inventore ipsa tempora, harum. Quidem repudiandae ex molestias fugiat et nihil cupiditate necessitatibus accusantium itaque non ipsam numquam consequatur pariatur enim, cumque.', 'question' : '10. Given Council’s adoption of the 10-year Housing and Homelessness Action Plan how would you advocate for increased housing opportunities for all Hamiltonians?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Land Transfer Tax',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Accusantium fugiat deserunt quisquam neque animi iste nam porro, iure, natus provident ipsa voluptate, sit illum nisi reiciendis consectetur eum delectus odio?', 'question' : '11. New Research has found that, if enacted, the municipal land transfer tax in Hamilton will lead to the loss of $342 million in economic activity and a reduction of $176 million in GDP. If elected as Mayor, will you protect affordable home ownership and commit to not bringing a municipal land transfer tax to Hamilton?'},
      { 'questionStub' : 'Downtown Revitalization',  'answer' : 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Consequatur distinctio eaque nihil tempora iste eligendi est consectetur dolore perferendis! Fugiat eveniet inventore amet illum, minus possimus eligendi adipisci eius provident.', 'question' : '12. How do you envision the role of a revitalizing downtown core as a key pillar of Hamilton’s economic future and what policy goals will you champion to further facilitate it?'}
    ]
  }
}); 
